1 9 9 1 年
越 南 岘 港
喂 这都是你干的吗?
Hello, did you do all of this?
贝瑞塔93
Beretta 93
通常都很可靠
Usually dependable.
我们现在可以走了
We should be good to go now.
来吧
Come on.
不要害怕
Don't be afraid.
三  十  年  后
罗 马 尼 亚, 布 加 勒 斯 特
搞什么? 你在开派对吗?
What the fuck? Are you having a party?
安东在哪里?
Where is Anton?
他为什么不接电话?
Why didn't he answer the phone?
瓦利
Vali!
你父亲在找你
Your father is looking for you.
起来
Get up!
起来 瓦利
Get up, Vali!
快点 姑娘们 快点 回家吧
Come on, girls, come on. Go home.
离开 离开 快点 离开这里
Away, away! Come on, get out of here.
快点瓦利 我们走
Come on Vali, let's go.
安东?
Anton?
瓦利在他妈哪里?
Where the fuck is Vali?
你在看着他 瓦利他妈的在哪?
You had to look over him, where the fuck is Vali?
什么事?
Yes?
谁在说话?
Who's talking?
是我 瓦利
It's me, Vali.
瓦利?
Vali?
给我解释你去哪了? 你为什么不...
Explain to me where did you go? Why don't you...
一些混蛋在酒店外面绑架了我
Some assholes kidnapped me outside the hotel.
什么? 是谁?
What? Who?
谁绑架了你?
Who kidnapped you?
我他妈怎么知道?
How they fuck would I know?
他们现在想要300万欧元
They want three million euros now.
瓦利 告诉他们我是干啥的
Vali, tell them how I am.
他们根本不在乎你是谁 只是付钱
They don't fucking care who you are, just pay!
他们想在两小时内拿到三百万欧元
They want three million euros in two hours.
否则他们会像杀猪一样割断我的喉咙
Or they'll cut my throat like a pig.
你们怎敢绑架我的孩子?
How dare you take my boy?
就在那里 你想数一数吗?
There it is. You wanna count it?
你知道我是谁吗?
Do you know who I am?
唐·普雷达
Don Preda.
布加勒斯特的屠夫 男人中的杀手
Butcher of Bucharest, Killer of Men.
告诉你老板事情办妥了
Tell your boss it's done.
你们到底是谁?
Exactly, who are you people?
我们只是...
We're just...
我们只是找到那些不想被找到的人
We just find people who can't be found.
钱
The money.
你们可能拿到钱一个小时
You gonna have it maybe for an hour.
我们就会把它拿回来
Then we come take it back,
然后把你俩切成碎片 拿去喂我的猪
cut you both into pieces and feed you to my pigs.
你不担心吗?
That doesn't worry you?
不
No.
为什么?
Why?
我来这里不是为了钱
I didn't come here for money.
我是来找你的
I came here for you.
拦住那个女孩 她杀了唐·普雷达 杀了她
Stop the girl. She killed Don Preda. Kill her.
你打架为啥这么厉害?
Why are you fighting so hard, huh?
你回家去吧 混蛋 滚
You're going home, motherfucker. Fuck off!
我很好
I'm good.
你他妈的混球 你不能把我扔在这里
You fucking pieces of shit. You can't leave me here!
去你妈的 你们这些混蛋
Fuck you, you bastards!
你拿到了吗?
Did you take any, huh?
拿到什么?
Take what?
钱
Money.
都在那里 对吧?
It was all there, right?
我们拿钱干掉目标 我们做这个
We were paid to eliminate the target. We did that.
对 知道吗 三百万... 脏钱... 没有人在找...
Yeah, you know, three mil... dirty money... nobody's looking for...
只是说说而已
Just saying.
噢 抱歉 我不知道你受伤了
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't know you're hurting.
拜托
Please.
这是RD管道公司 你的漏水问题已修复
This is R & D Plumbing. Your leak has been fixed.
请将您的付款余额汇到...
Please remit the balance of your payment for the withd...
700万欧元转账完成
搞定
Done.
咳嗽这个事你要去看医生
You need to see a doctor about that cough.
看医生还是看女巫?
Traditional or a witch?
比如你? 绝对是个女巫
You? Definitely a witch.
我只认识可以联系的巫毒女王
I know just the voodoo queen to call.
伦     敦
切姆斯福德简直是个血腥战区
Chelmsford was a bloody war zone.
每趟车都晚点30分钟 永远拥挤不堪
Every train was 30 minutes late and jam-packed as always.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
谢谢你照顾她
Thank you for taking care of her,
你知道你是她唯一接受的人 对吧?
you know you're the only one she'll tolerate, right?
你不在的时候 她变得很调皮
She gets really mean when you're away.
我大部分时间都和普鲁斯特在一起
Spent most of the time hanging out with Proust.
是真的吗?
Is that true?
三个星期 这就是你带回来的全部?
Three weeks, and this is all you come back with?
啊 你知道卖家
Ah, you know sellers,
他们知道你大老远来的 就故意摆谱
they know you've come all that way, and they play hard to get.
你有杀了他们的想法吗?
Didn't you wanna just kill people like that?
你以为你在干什么?
What do you think you're doing, huh?
前几天 他对我说 “70岁就像30岁”
So, the other day, he says to me "70 is the new 30."
嗯 那只是老家伙哄人的话
Well, that's just something old guys say.
他守协议了吗? 他是按照医嘱做的吗?
How is he doing with his protocol? Is he following the doctor's orders?
更像是按他自己的规矩做
More like, following his own orders.
生日快乐...
Happy birth...
再也没有该死的生日了
No more fucking birthdays.
带上生日 让它们见鬼去吧
Take birthdays and shove them up your ass.
混蛋
Bastard.
多美妙的玩具啊
What a wonderful toy!
在蜡烛上我看到了你们的吝啬
You skimped on the candles I see.
七十支蜡烛会是火灾隐患
Seventy would have been a fire hazard.
请给我们沏茶好吗?
Could you make us some tea please?
当然
Sure.
好吧 许个愿吧
All right, make your wish.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
是啊
Yeah.
谢谢你
To thank you.
1958年的吉布森飞翔V
A 1958 Gibson Flying V.
这款仅生产了两年
This was in production just two years.
全世界只有90把
There is only 90 in the whole world.
我知道
I know.
那声音...
That sound...
它是木质的
It's the wood.
非洲榄仁木
African limba.
独一无二的音质
Nothing else sounds like it.
我只是想放弃寻找一个希望
I was just about giving up hope on finding one.
你到底是怎么...
How in the world did you...
你
You.
你教我如何找到不想被发现的东西
You taught me how to find things that didn't wanna be found.
阿尔伯特·金用过这款
Albert King played one.
阿尔伯特·金用过这把
Albert King played that one.
不
No!
你现在要哭了 是吗?
You're gonna cry now, aren't you?
只是因为我没法按正确的方式演奏
Only because I can't play it the way it needs to be played.
谢谢你
Thank you.
昨晚双胞胎中的一个打电话给我 说她怀孕了
One of the twins called me last night, said she was pregnant.
多佛的黛西?
Daisy in Dover?
不 黛西在曼彻斯特
No, Daisy in Manchester.
多佛的黛西是个女同
Daisy in Dover is a dyke.
有个足够信任你的朋友在你提出要求前
It is a rare gift to have a friend who trusts you enough
不会去尝试帮助 这是份难得的礼物
not to try and help until you ask.
如果你和那些人一起掉进池塘 你会淹死的
If you fell in the pond with those you'd drown.
哦 如果我掉在没有他们的池塘里 我可能会漂走
Well, if I fell in a pond without them I would probably float away.
- 嗨 亲爱的  - 小心手指
- Hi, honey.  - Mind your fingers.
会咬人
That hefa bites.
她还是个婴儿 什么都不知道
She's a baby and doesn't know any better.
这里
There.
你有自己的秘密藏身处
You have your own secret hideout.
为什么我不感到惊讶?
Why am I not surprised?
我买下了这幢房子
I bought the building.
- 什么?  - 书店
- What?  - The bookstore.
它是你的 免费又干净
It's yours. Free and clear.
你不必那么做
You didn't have to do that.
我知道 但这是你的爱好
I know, but it's your passion.
而且 知道这一点让我感觉很好
And, it makes me feel good to know
我不在的时候你会有事情做
you'll have something to work on while I'm gone.
那是什么?
What is that?
那些是在另一边等我的灵魂
Those are the souls waiting for me on the other side.
我肯定他们已经安排好了招待会
I'm sure they have a reception planned.
啊... 过早的送走了这么多人
Ah... sent away so many prematurely.
要么通过我的手 要么通过你的
Either by my hand or through you.
我们从来没有送走任何一个不必送走的人
We never sent anyone away who didn't have it coming.
也许吧
Maybe.
但是... 我相信那里一定有不少人
But... I'm sure there are quite a few spirits up there
在心怀愤懑的等着我
waiting for me with a bone to pick.
你真的相信你会去那里吗?
You really believe you're going up?
你不信吗?
Don't you?
卢卡斯·海耶斯
Lucas Hayes.
告诉我们的朋友帮我找到他
I need our friend to find him for me.
我只查到他1998年在巴黎 之后就没有踪迹了
I have him up till 1998, Paris, after that nothing.
- 只是找到吗?  - 只是找到
- Just find?  - Just find.
谨慎 而且要尽快
Discreetly, and with the quickness.
好吧
Okay.
我可能得回越南了
I may have to go back to Vietnam.
如果你和我一起去就好了
It'd be nice if you went with me.
我再也不回那里了
I'm never going back there.
小变色龙 我们的过去永远都不会改变
Our past is never where we left it, little chameleon.
我们都有伤疤
We all have scars.
你盯着它们看久点 就会记得是在哪里得到的
You stare at them long enough you remember how you got them.
- 嗨  - 早
- Hi.  - Morning.
这件蓝色连衣裙有个小口子 我想和本尼谈谈
The blue dress has a small tear in it, I was hoping to talk to Benny about it.
你怎么看?
What do you think?
什么?
Of what?
我的 胡子
My, mustache.
噢 知道吗 我没有戴隐形眼镜 抱歉
Oh, you know, I don't have my contacts in, sorry.
有趣
Funny.
你等着像你这样的女人长大...
You wait till this grows in women like you are gonna be so...
不 没关系 我会帮你的
No, it's okay. I'll help you out.
我要你找到这人
I need you to find this guy.
什么? 没有布加勒斯特城外黑手党据点的卫星照片?
What? No satellite shots of a mafia compound outside Bucharest?
没有 但那是你的拿手好戏
No, but that was some of your better work.
穆迪想找这个叫卢卡斯·海耶斯的人
Moody wants this guy, Lucas Hayes,
最后出现是98年在巴黎 然后就消失了
last seen in Paris in '98 and then nothing.
是啊
Yeah.
我马上就来
I'll be with you in a second.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
是的 我在找一本书
Yeah, I'm looking for a book,
一本旧书 像“半熟的”
an old book. Like, rare.
rare : "稀有 罕见"的意思 也有"半生半熟"的意思
- “像半熟”?  - 对
- "Like rare"?  - Yeah.
要么有 要么没有
Either they are or they aren't.
书不像牛排 你不可能买到半生不熟的书
Books aren't like stake, you can't get them like medium rare.
- 真有趣  - 讽刺
- It's funny.  - Sarcastic.
是的 但很有趣
Yes, but funny.
听着 我老板的妻子在开派对 她收集书籍 初版
Listen, my boss' wife is having a party and she collects books, first editions.
- 有具体的名字吗?  - 鸟 是奥杜邦的...
- Any particular subject?  - Birds. It's Audobon's...
- 《美国鸟类》?  - 对 就是它
- "Birds of America"?  - Yeah, that's it.
他说她在找副本
He said she's looking for a copy.
- 初版的?  - 对
- A first edition?  - Yeah.
- 抱歉  - 你没有吗?
- Sorry.  - You don't have it?
没人会有 只有一个初版存在
No one does, only one first editions exists,
1991年 它以960万澳元的价格卖给了一位私人买家
it was sold to a private buyer in 1991 for a 9.6 million dollars.
哇 好吧
Wow, okay.
看来我运气不好
Well, looks like I'm out of luck.
好吧 你有建议吗? 或许诗歌也行?
All right. What do you think? Maybe poetry?
稍等...
Hang on...
这会是派对上的热点
It'll be the hit of the party.
《帖木儿及其他诗》
我不... 我不了解这本诗
I don't... I don't know this one.
是埃德加·爱伦·坡的
It's Edgar Allan Poe actually.
他的第一本诗集是匿名出版的
His first collection of poems published anonymously.
你觉得她可能要吗?
You think she might have it?
据说只印了50本 并且现存的只有12本
Doubtful. Only 50 copies were printed. Only 12 are known to exist.
多少钱?
How much?
我可以26万5千美元给你
I can give it to you for $265,000.
要不送个手镯?
Perhaps a bracelet instead?
她的手腕确实很精致 好主意
She does have exquisite wrists, good idea.
还有别的事吗?
Is there something else?
我发现你很有趣
I find you interesting.
- 你是说...  - 你很有趣
- You mean...  - You're interesting.
漂亮 当然 不是那种表面性的
Beautiful, sure, not in that ornamental kind of way.
是吸引力那部分 让我想知道
It's the interesting part that got me wondering.
想知道什么?
Wondering what?
我给你我的电话号码后 你要多久来决定
How long after I give you my number will it take you
我也同样有吸引力并给我打电话?
to decide that I'm just as interesting and give me a call?
二十七分钟
Twenty seven minutes.
那么长?
That long?
首先我得假装取消约会 然后我得喂我的猫
First I have to pretend to cancel my date and then I have to feed my cat.
那只要六分钟
That's six.
剩下的就是我在矜持
The rest is me playing hard to get.
可爱
Cute.
你带了多少张 先生...
How many of these are you carrying around, Mr...
我叫伦勃朗 迈克尔·伦勃朗
Rembrandt. Michael Rembrandt.
实际上 直到刚才我才有机会用到它
Actually, I haven't had an occasion to use one until just now.
所以...
So...
吸引力
Interesting.
“曾经有一座喷泉升起
"There rose a fountain once,
诗句正是出自爱伦坡的《帖木儿及其他诗》
那里有许多美丽的花朵抬起头”
and there full many a fair flower raised its head."
那出自书中 是不是
That was from the book, wasn't it.
“但养育它们的她早已死去
"But she who rear'd them was long dead,
并不知道现在的愚蠢”
And in such follies had no part."
这一次你差点难倒我
You almost got me on this one.
你没说我会追踪一个8岁的孩子
You didn't say I'd be tracking an eight year old.
卢卡斯·海耶斯确实在98年到过巴黎
Lucas Hayes did arrive in Paris in '98,
但在1999年3月回到了岘港
but returned to Da Nang, March '99.
所有的东西都在上面
Everything else I have is on there.
B.B·金  村门俱乐部音乐会现场
准备 出发
本尼?
Benny?
你先别睡等我到那里 45分钟
You'll stay up until I get there, 45 minutes.
卢卡斯·海耶斯 1990年4月5日出生
父亲：爱德华·海耶斯
母亲：玛丽·克里斯蒂安
圣基特里娅医院
卢卡斯·海耶斯
1999年6月2日住进圣基特里娅医院
父亲：爱德华·海耶斯 1991年圣诞节遇刺 没有其他记录
爱德华·亚瑟·海耶斯
因战争罪被起诉的商人死于汽车炸弹袭击
爱德华·海耶斯... 昨天在岘港的一次汽车爆炸中丧生
穆迪
Moody.
“公司将继续前进”首席执行官发誓
沃尔说：“爱德华·海耶斯是我25年的搭档”
我将继续像他希望的那样领导我们的公司”
乔西诺·沃尔
越  南  岘  港
该死 那是他妈的什么?
Shit! What the fuck is that?
妈的
Fuck.
亲爱的 来吧
Honey! Come on.
没想到我会在这里再见到你
Never thought I'd see you here again.
也许你现在不想看见我
Well, maybe you're not seeing me now.
这婊子是谁?
Who's the bitch?
比利小子...
Billy Boy...
我知道你和各色人等混 但现在你和蠢货混吗?
I know you run with all kinds but now you're running with stupid?
去你的
Fuck you!
嘿 去喝一杯 宝贝 给大人一点私密时间 好吗?
Hey! Go get a drink, sugar, and give the adults some privacy, huh?
啤酒
Beers!
外面是你的摩托吗?
Is that your ride outside?
现在是你的了
Yours now.
今天不是我生日
It ain't my birthday.
乔西诺·沃尔
Jossino Vohl.
穆迪怎么样?
How's Moody?
他死了
He's dead.
敬穆迪
For Moody.
沃尔牵涉其中吗?
Vohl involved?
我不知道 但他知道是谁牵涉其中
I don't know. But he knows who is.
- 他很难被干掉  - 我只是想和他谈谈
- He's gonna be hard to kill.  - I just wanna talk to him.
斯蒂夫里诺
Steverino!
什么事 老板?
Yeah, Boss?
你在国家大厦当保安
You work security at the State Tower.
我的朋友需要和沃尔呆几分钟
My friend there needs a few minutes with Vohl.
单独
Alone.
是啊 那不可能
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
没有贴身保镖 他哪儿也不去
He goes nowhere without private security.
这家伙从不单独一人
The guy's never alone.
怎么了?
What is happening?
对我来说很容易找到你 沃尔先生
This is how easy it is for me to get to you, Mr. Vohl.
你明白吗?
Do you understand?
你是爱德华·海耶斯的朋友和商业伙伴
You were friends and business partners with Edward Hayes,
所以你对他短暂而有趣的一生了解最多
so you would know most about his short but interesting life.
很好 因为我有问题
Good, cause I have questions.
你给我的答案 如果我满意 你就不会再见到我
You give me answers: if I'm satisfied you'll never see me again,
如果我不满意 我就是你见到的最后一个人
if I'm not, I'll be the last thing you'll ever see.
我期待着你的回复
I look forward to hearing from you.
晚上好 小姐
Good evening, Miss.
很久都没有这么
It's been a long time since such
漂亮的年轻女子给我她的电话号码了
a beautiful young woman gave me her number.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
乔西诺·沃尔 生于1945年4月
Jossino Vohl, born in April, 1945.
法国国民 长期住在越南
French national, residing full time in Vietnam.
和爱德华·海耶斯做生意
Was in business with Edward Hayes
直到他英年早逝
until his untimely death.
现在你是顶级政治权力经纪人
Now you're a top political power broker
有一些有趣的业余爱好
with some interesting side hobbies.
看来你对我的简历很熟悉
I see you're familiar with my resume.
我对你的商业活动不感兴趣 沃尔先生
I am not interested in your business activities, Mr. Vohl.
我想谈谈你朋友的儿子 卢卡斯
I want to talk about your friend's son, Lucas.
来我办公室 一小时后
My office, one hour.
我们单独谈吗?
We'll be alone?
我的律师会在场
My lawyer will be present.
就是站在你身后给你倒苏格兰威士忌的那个人?
That would be the man standing behind you pouring a scotch?
很高兴 小姐
Delighted, Miss.
正好准时
Exactly on time.
请
Please.
杜凯先生 我的私人律师
Monsieur Duquet, my personal attorney.
- 你想来点香槟吗?  - 爱德华·亚瑟·海耶斯
- Would you like some champagne?  - Edward Arthur Hayes.
埃迪和我一起参与了一个铝土矿开采项目
Eddie and I were involved in a bauxite mining project together
直到他出意外
until his accident.
那不是意外 是暗杀
It wasn't an accident, it was an assassination.
我们一直提供帮助
We were useful.
这个国家具有可塑性 适合某些商业实践
The country was malleable, ripe for certain business practices.
埃迪正在处理许多敏感问题
Eddie was juggling a lot of delicate plates.
你对一个已经死了将近三十年的人有什么兴趣?
What's your interest in a man who's been dead almost thirty years?
我对他儿子感兴趣
I'm interested in his son.
卢卡斯·海耶斯
Lucas Hayes.
说什么?
I'm sorry?
有三个人死了 因为他们都打听过他
Three people are dead because they inquired about him.
他杀了他们 所以我要去找他
He had them killed and I'm going to find him.
我应该和他谈谈吗?
Should I be talking to him?
我和卢卡斯·海耶斯没有联系
I have no connection with Lucas Hayes.
而这跟我有什么关系?
And what does any of this got to do with me?
我也想知道原因
I was wondering the same thing.
沃尔先生过去的关系与任何人无关
Mr. Vohl's past relationships are no one's concern.
当然也与你无关
And certainly none of yours.
噢 我已经让它成为我的关注点了
Oh, I've made them my concern.
很遗憾
Too bad.
我需要知道一切
I need to know everything.
你是谁?
Who are you?
谁雇了你?
Who hired you?
为什么对卢卡斯·海耶斯感兴趣?
Why the interest in Lucas Hayes?
如果你愿意 我们可以用另一种方式
We can do this another way if you'd like.
他妈的放开我
Fucking let me go!
上去
Get up there.
递给我一把枪
Hand me a gun.
喷 水 阀
你他妈以为你能去哪里?
Where the fuck do you think you're going?
说吧
Say it.
- 去你的  - 说吧
- Fuck you!  - Say it!
她在下面
She's down there!
我们从你的名字开始
Let's start with your name.
穆迪为什么要找爱德华·海耶斯的儿子?
Why was Moody looking for Edward Hayes' son?
我们还应该知道哪些人?
Who else out there should we know about?
妈的
Fuck!
有谁能坚持这么久
Anyone ever last this long.
反正现也不在我们的控制中了
It's out of our hands now, anyway.
他呢?
Him?
那是个漫长的27分钟
That was a long 27 minutes.
我还在等你的电话
I'm still waiting for your call.
没关系
It's all right.
我不认为这些事是针对个人的
I don't take these things personally.
骨汤
Bone broth.
有助于减轻炎症和瘀伤
Helps with inflammation and bruising.
给
Here.
小心 很烫 小心点
Careful. It's hot. Watch it.
好了
There you go.
我也喜欢喝这个
I like this myself.
好了 小口喝
Here you go, small sips.
还好吗?
Good?
我不会骗你
Not gonna lie to you,
这对你来说没有太多的机会
there's not much of a chance this ends well for you.
外面那个家伙
That guy out there.
我们为同一个人工作
We work for the same individual.
老板有问题 就给他打电话 他会处理
Boss has a problem. He calls him, he takes care of it.
对我来说这有点重口 但这不是我决定的
Little heavy handed for my taste but that's not my call.
你的朋友穆迪的事 我感到抱歉
I'm sorry about your friend, Moody.
我没有参与那件事
I had no part in that.
或者书店的火灾
Or the fire fight at the bookstore.
我是个专门善后的人
I'm an after-the-facts guy.
我来这里是为确保没有遗留问题
I come in to make sure there's no loose ends.
我发现那些看似无害 但实际并非如此的事物
I look for things that might seem benign, but aren't.
比如一个杀手经营的书店 我从来没意识到这点
Like a bookstore run by an assassin, boy, I never saw that one coming.
我完全误解了你
I misread you completely.
我可以帮你离开这里
I can help you out of here.
好吗?
Okay?
但是你也必须帮我
But you have to help me.
我是你最后的防线
I'm your last line of defense.
路的尽头 不再有生机
End of the road, no more lifelines.
你明白吗?
You understand?
好吧
All right.
你忘了焯骨头
You forgot to blanch the bones.
你的汤
Your soup.
你必须先把骨头焯一下再烤
You have to blanch the bones before you roast them.
这样才能锁住矿物质 增加愈合效果
Locks the minerals in, it's better for healing.
你从她那里有收获吗?
You got anything out of her?
是与不
Yes and no.
这他妈是什么意思?
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
意味着我明天早上会回来跟她继续谈
Means I'll be back in the morning to follow up with her.
- 我不需要你在这里 伦勃朗  - 哦...
- I don't need you here, Rembrandt.  - Well...
在支票上签字的人不这么想
The man who signs the checks thought differently.
- 噢 是吗?  - 对
- Oh, yeah?  - Yeah.
为什么会这样?
And why is that?
噢 我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
也许是因为你未经他的同意就杀了沃尔
Maybe it's because you killed Vohl without asking his permission.
沃尔知道一切 他有个直接的联系
Vohl knew everything, he was a direct connection.
会像帐篷一样折叠起来
Would've folded like a tent.
你... 是的 杀了我 你们还是一样 先开枪 再提问
You... yes, kill me, you're all the same: shoot first and ask questions later.
尽量不要用那些强化的审讯手段
And hold off on those enhanced interrogation techniques.
我希望她早上头脑清醒
I want her clear-headed in the morning.
他明天会毁掉她
He'll break her tomorrow.
也许他已经毁掉她了
Maybe he broke her already.
老头子非常想弄清她知道些什么
The old man is desperate to know what she knows.
我想知道如果他的小子在他查清前杀了她 会是什么感觉
I wonder how it'd feel if his boy wonder ends up killing her before he finds out.
我猜他会找一个新的神奇小子
I'm guessing he'll look for a new boy wonder.
就在我们刚认识的时候
Just when we were getting to know each other.
我在机场 造船厂和火车站都有小组
I've got teams at the airport, shipyard and train station.
她不会跑 她会治愈自己的伤
She's not gonna run, she's gonna lick her wounds.
然后她就会来找你
Then she's coming after you.
很好
Good.
真的?
Really?
因为现在是4比0 她领先
Cause right now it's 4:0. She's wining.
你在哪里买的西装?
Where do you buy your suits?
因为我有一个高大的表弟
Cause I've got a cousin as big and tall
他过得很艰难
and he's a hard time.
家里没人
Nobody's home.
我可以带你去边境
Well, I can get you to the border.
伦敦现在对你来说可能不安全
London may not be safe for you right now.
这是越南 安娜
This is Vietnam, Anna,
你知道这里是什么样的
you know what's it like here.
你不能死 你欠穆迪的
You owe it to Moody to stay alive.
我知道我欠他什么
I know what I owe him.
走吧
Go.
你他妈以为我给你钱是为...
The fuck you think I gave you the money of...
旅途结束了 孩子
End of the line, kid.
进去
Get in!
小心
Watch out!
穆迪很棒
Moody was beautiful,
以他的方式
in his way.
他人很好
He was kind.
他不是通过努力 这就是他身份的一部分
And not through effort, it was just a part of who he was.
他没有救我的命 而是他给了我新生
He didn't save my life, he gave me a life.
他知道我是谁 会成为什么
He knew who I was, what I've become.
他保护我
And he protected me.
海耶斯已经死了三十年了
Hayes has been dead for thirty years,
沃尔消失很久了
Vohl was gone longer.
有一些非常坏的人在找你
You've got some very bad people looking for you.
卢卡斯·海耶斯杀了穆迪
Lucas Hayes killed Moody,
他知道我在找他
he knows I'm looking for him.
他最后出现的地点是圣基特里娅医院
His last known location is St. Quiteria Hospital.
没有人比那些不想听见的人更聋
Nobody is as deaf as those who don't wanna listen.
你好 阮女士
Hello, Ms. Nguyen.
我们已经有段时间没有受到卫生部的访问了
It's been some time since we've had a visit from the Ministry of Health.
以及询问过去的记录...
And to request records from that far back...
是的 我知道
Yes, I know.
我们希望能找到一些能帮我们排除
We're hoping to find something in there that will help us
环境因素的资料 因为我们正在进行一项研究
rule out environmental factors, cause we are in the midst of a study.
谢谢
Thank you.
卢卡斯·海耶斯 在我来这里前就在
Lucas Hayes, well before my time here.
2585024586
2585024586.
收到 我会查找文档
Copy, I'll get Doc on it.
好
Okay.
文档找到了 查了他的记录
Doc came through, pulled his records.
然后呢?
And?
如下
Sit down:
卢卡斯·海耶斯于1999年6月2日进入圣基特里娅医院
Lucas Hayes was admitted to St. Quiteria on 2nd June, 1999,
根据他的记录 他从未离开过
and according to his records never left.
抱歉 看来那孩子是以克里斯蒂安的名字重新注册的
I apologize, seems the boy was re-admitted under the name Christian.
克里斯蒂安 对 他母亲的娘家姓
Christian, right, his mother's maiden name.
我来的时候他已经在这里了
He was already here when I arrived,
他做了二十多年的病人
been a patient for more than twenty years.
他不喜欢被触摸
He doesn't like to be touched.
他无法说话 又聋又瞎
He can't speak. Also deaf and blind.
他这样有多久了?
And how long has he been like this?
他六岁时被确诊 我相信 病情迅速恶化了
He was diagnosed when he was six, I believe, it regressed rapidly.
他能活这么久真是个奇迹
It's a miracle he's lived as long.
谁在支付他的护理费用?
And who pays for his care?
我们有个慷慨的捐助人
We have a generous endowment.
这里的每个人都是免费的
Everyone here is treated for free.
哇 四个人死了 监控上什么都没有
Wow! Four men dead, nothing on camera.
这地方看起来像个屠宰场
Place looks like an abattoir.
是食物吗?
Was it the food?
知道吗 那样很无礼
You know, it was bad manners.
对 那可不是对待淑女的好方式
Yeah, well, that's no way to treat a lady.
我不是淑女
I'm no lady.
不是说我就是个绅士
Not that I was a gentleman myself.
我不会像你那么谦虚
I wouldn't sell yourself short.
你说出来 就是种称赞
Coming from you, that's a compliment.
我还有事要做...
I'm in the middle of something...
嘿 圣基特里娅的好姐妹们怎么样?
Hey, how were good sisters of the St. Quiteria?
好得足以让我知道我找错人了
Good enough to let me know I've been looking for the wrong person.
都是好姑娘
Good gals out there.
圣基特里娅 你知道她是谁吗?
St. Quiteria, do you know who she was?
她15岁时领导了一场反抗罗马军团的游击战
Fifteen years old, she led a guerrilla war against the Roman legions.
坏蛋
Bad ass.
他们砍了她的头 把剩下的拿去喂狗
They chopped off her head and fed the rest to the dogs.
再说一次 那很无礼
Again, bad manners.
嘿 你要来吃晚饭吗?
Hey, you up for a dinner?
我可以回答问题并节省你的时间
I could answer some questions and save you some time.
在米其林餐厅怎么样? 明晚八点
What do say if we say La Cinq? Tomorrow night, eight o'clock.
我是说你可以建议 但我不会去
I mean you can say it. But I won't be there.
我会给你一个时间和地点
I'll give you the time and place.
你对她很感兴趣
You're intrigued by her.
是好奇
Curious.
我需要担心吗?
Need I worry?
晚会名单 先生 200位嘉宾 都检查过了
The gala list, sir, 200 guests, all vetted.
满屋子富人和特权人士为崇高事业
The joys of a room full of the wealthy and the privileged
捐赠大笔款项的这种乐趣
donating large sums for a noble cause.
永远不会过时
Never gets old.
很好
Good.
你为什么这么做?
Why did you do this?
这是我这个位置的人应该做的 迈克尔
It's what people in my position are supposed to do, Michael.
给那些不幸的人
Give to the less fortunate.
我是问我是否应该担心
I asked if I should be worried.
关于那个女人
About the woman.
不
Nope.
还不用
Not yet.
请在周日前让这个不愉快的事结束
Please wrap up this unpleasantness by Sunday.
我不想在庆典前感到尴尬
I don't wanna be embarrassed before the celebration.
哇
Wow.
谢谢你 本
Thank you, Ben.
他们知道我在这里
They know me here.
干杯
Cheers.
有人杀了我的一个朋友
Someone killed a friend of mine
因为他几年前完成的一份合同
because of a contract he completed years ago.
和我谈过这件事的人最后都死了
And anyone I ask about it ends up dead.
那是为什么?
Why is that?
我不知道 但有些人可能会把它当作一种迹象
I don't know, but some people might take it as a sign.
你为什么不认为这是个无解的谜团?
Why don't you just consider it a mystery best left unsolved?
但我喜欢解谜
But I like mysteries.
我开始做这个的时候只是好奇
When I started this I was curios.
接着我从好奇变成了关心
And then I went from curious to concerned.
现在呢?
And now?
我不耐烦了
I'm testy.
相信我 我不耐烦时你不想见到我
An trust me, you don't wanna know me when I'm testy.
赫克勒-科赫9毫米
HK 9mm.
很好
Very good.
这不适合我
Not from where I'm sitting.
谁在为孤儿买单? 我想和他谈谈
Who's paying for the orphan kid? I'd like to talk to whoever that is.
那事不明智的
That'd be unwise.
“不明智”杀了一个对我来说就像父亲的人
Unwise is killing a man who was a second father to me.
我们都不再“不明智”了
We are way past unwise.
这是个很糟糕的行动地点
This is a really bad place for a hit.
高档餐厅 每个出口都有保安 更不用说摄像头了
High-end restaurant, the security at every exit, not to mention the cameras.
你知道的 你已经知道那些了
You know what, you already knew that.
噢 我不是来杀你的...
Oh, I'm not here to kill you...
只是为了得到答案
Yet. Just to get answers.
你总是这样问?
You always ask like this?
对 我喜欢在和人谈话时引起对方注意 你知道吗?
Yeah, I like to have peoples' attention when I talk, you know?
好吧...
Well...
你肯定引起了下面那些人的注意
you certainly have the attention of the boys down there.
听着 你至少得朝我开三枪才能确保安全
Look, you're gonna have to put at least three in me to be sure.
四枪
Four.
好 剩下五颗子弹 万一有麻烦
Fine. That leaves you with five. In case there's trouble.
你觉得这些子弹足以让你离开这里吗?
You think that's enough to get you out of here?
四发快射 然后在混乱中慢慢地走向出口 行
Four quick shots and then the slow walk to the exit amongst the chaos. Yeah.
但必须考虑到意外情况
Something unexpected could happen.
知道吗 通常是这样
You know, it usually does.
西格226 射速很快
SIG 226, it's got that great kick.
对
Yeah.
怎么样 我们第一次尴尬的沉默
How about that. Our first awkward silence.
你知道吗 我还不知道你的名字
You know what, I didn't get your name.
安娜
Anna.
- 幸会  - 我们拭目以待
- Pleasure.  - We'll see.
你说我们忘了这些把戏如何
What do you say we forget these tricks.
去找一家不错的旅馆
Let's just go for a nice hotel.
你用枪指着我的小妹妹然后要我上床?
You point a gun at my pussy and then you ask me to bed?
我喜欢你的风格
I like your style.
是说那个女人用中空弹指着我的蛋蛋
Said the woman with hollow-points pointed at my balls.
好吧 希望这不会变得太糟 这是我最喜欢的鞋子
Well, let's hope this doesn't get messy. These are my favorite shoes.
马诺洛 经典四英寸高跟
Manolo's, classic four inch pumps.
一个懂爱伦·坡和鞋子的人
A man who knows Poe and footwear.
让我小心翼翼的告诉你
Let me put this to you delicately,
你继续这样 你会死的
you keep this up, you're gonna die.
越南一直是死亡之地
Vietnam has always been a place of death.
只有幸运的人才活着出去 我曾经很幸运
Only lucky ones make it out alive. I was lucky once.
你不会两次都走运
You don't get lucky twice.
我要找出谁杀了我的朋友
I'm going to find out who killed my friend.
你找到之后呢?
And when you do?
我要结束他们的生命
I'm going to end their life,
以及任何挡我路的人
and anyone standing in my way.
感谢你度过一个愉快的夜晚
Thank you for a lovely evening.
嘿 我知道这听起来很疯狂
Hey, I know it sounds crazy,
但我真的很想在
but I'd really like to see you again
不同的场景下再见到你
under, you know, different circumstances.
这是私人时间
This was personal time.
这是你见过我的最好场景
So these are the best circumstances you'll ever see me in.
说吧
Speak.
完成后给我打电话
Call me when it's done.
我以为你要去追腐败的会计师
I thought you're off chasing corrupt accountants.
我发现一个酒店房间里有她所有东西 包括她的护照
I found a hotel room with all of her shit, including her passport.
我叫娜迪亚·朱科娃
Name's Nadia Zhukova.
亚裔俄罗斯人
An Asian Russian.
小子
Boy.
你从来没有真正看到过
You don't really see that ever.
干得好 你一定很累吧?
Good work, you must be exhausted, huh?
看来我晚了一天
Looks like I'm a day late.
你来晚了  恐怕没有活口了
And a dollar short. Didn't take much I'm afraid.
他像只鸟一样叽喳 不是吗?
He sang like a bird, didn't he?
我现在知道一切
All of the things I know now.
我知道你的老板是谁
I know who your boss is,
批准杀了穆迪的人
the man who sanctioned Moody's killing.
他是条大鱼
He's a big fish.
你钓他时会更有趣
More fun when you hook him.
好吧 那么我想...
Well, then I guess...
我想我们很快就会见面了
I guess we'll be seeing each other real soon then.
比你想象的要快
Sooner than you think.
嘿 你的手怎么了?
Hey, what happened to your hand?
做决定吧
Make up your mind:
杀我还是上我?
Kill me or fuck me?
真奇怪 我们在这家伙的床上 而他...
It's so weird that we're in this guy's bed while he's...
在上面
up there.
你知道 挂起来
You know, hanging.
不
No.
那会浪费一张好床
Would be a waste of a nice bed.
好吧
Okay.
你干这个多久了?
How long have you been doing this?
你知道 不是指这个 但...
Not, you know, this, but...
久到不会出错
Long enough not to miss.
你很幸运
You got lucky.
不
Nah.
你不想让我死
You don't want me dead.
但是
Yet.
你为什么不杀我?
Why haven't you killed me?
你会吗?
Could you?
我可以在你后脑勺上开两枪 做个三明治
I could put two in the back of your head and go make a sandwich.
哦
Well.
你总是说这行不通
You always said this wasn't gonna work out.
不
No.
根据我的经验 它永远不会发生
It's been my experience, it never does.
至少对另一个人来说不会
At least not for the other guy.
有解决办法吗?
Have a way around that?
你手上有全部的牌
You are holding all the cards.
我正看见一个女人抓着一根
I'm watching a woman who walk over a shark tank
紧绷的绳子走过鲨鱼池
on a tight rope in high winds.
你不会成功的 安娜
You're not gonna make it, Anna.
他是个坏人
He's a bad man.
他做了很多坏事
Who's done very bad things.
所以 你就只是躺在那里?
So, you just gonna lay there?
很高兴见到你 孩子
Good to see you, kid.
进去 出来
Get in. Get out.
你知道你只有一次机会
You know you only get lucky once.
是啊 刚才有人告诉我了
Yeah. Someone else just told me that.
好吧
Okay.
上帝
God!
- 只是一点胶 只是点胶  - 你怎么回事
- Just a little glue. Just a little glue.  - What's wrong with you!
没事的 咬紧牙关
It's okay, grit your teeth.
噢 天哪
Oh, God.
知道吗 我仍然为克劳迪娅感到难过
You know, I still feel really bad about Claudia.
她做的饭很差劲 但她不该那样死
She couldn't cook worth a shit, but she didn't deserve to die like that.
好了
Here we go.
好
Okay.
好 总算结束了
Okay, okay. We're done here.
你真的认为他们可以轻易杀了我吗?
Did you really think they can kill me that easily?
在我动手之前 他的脸色就已经非常难看了
Before I blew the rest of it off he didn't have much of a face to begin with.
我留下了足够的线索
And I left just enough of me
让当局认为是我干的
for the authorities to think it was me.
很抱歉你发现了他
I'm sorry you had to be the one who found him.
不管怎样 你一直都反应敏捷
You could always think on your feet anyway.
但今晚没有
Not so much tonight.
这就是朋友的作用 对吧?
That's what friends are for, right?
噢 很好 我们又是朋友了
Oh, good. We're friends again.
你跟人上床了 是不是?
You got laid, didn't you?
越来越依赖这玩意儿
Depending more and more on this shit
来缓解症状
to take the edge off.
那么 计划是什么?
So, what's the plan?
四百英亩 去那里
Four hundred acres, to get there
你必须徒步穿越12英里老鼠出没的丛林
you'd have to hike through 12 miles of rat-infested jungle.
剩下的是河流 摄像机 声纳 巡逻艇
That leaves the river, cameras, sonar, patrol boats.
你还是个悲观的小混蛋 不是吗?
Still a pessimistic little shit, aren't you?
你还是一只杀不死的小强
And you're still a cockroach you can't kill.
我是说以一种好的方式
I mean it in a good way.
他们知道你要来
They know you're coming.
这是什么?
What is this?
它是个安全屋 也可以认为 它是个安全堡垒
It's a panic room, in this case it's a panic bunker.
如果他进去了 你就结束了
If he gets in there, you're done.
所有客人都是乘船来的
All the guests arrive by boat,
他们一下船就会接受检查
they'll be screened a moment they disembark.
整个地方都被锁定和保护
Perimeter locked down and site secured.
为了今晚 我又增加了一支来自以色列的16人团队
And I've added an additional team of 16 out of Israel just for the night.
看来你把一切都安排好了
Seems like you got everything covered.
迈克尔
Michael.
你的看法?
Thoughts?
威尼斯
Venice.
每年的这个季节真的很好
It's really nice this time of year.
你应该去 现在
You should go. Now.
这些人不知道他们在和谁打交道
These guys have no idea who they're dealing with.
收到
Copy that.
你看起来有点紧张
You look a little tense.
我保护从王储到卡特尔头目的所有人
I've protected everyone from crowned princes to cartel kingpins.
今晚什么都不会发生
Nothing's gonna happen tonight
尤其是我们已经知道她长什么样
especially when we know what she looks like.
小子...
Boy...
我真希望你拿到了预付款
I really hope you got paid upfront.
先生
Sir.
有情况吗?
Anything?
目前还没有 第一区 第二区和第三区安全
Nothing so far. Sectors one, two and three are clear.
我在等第四区的报告
I'm waiting on the reports from sector four.
谢谢
Thank you.
我非常高兴在这个重要的夜晚
It is with great pleasure that I welcome you all here
欢迎大家来到这里
on this very expensive evening.
看到这么多熟悉的面孔
It warms my crusty heart to look across
温暖了我这颗倔强的心
the room and see so many familiar faces,
亲爱的朋友 以及亲密的商业伙伴
dear friends, and close business associates.
还有不少陌生的面孔
As well as quite a few unfamiliar faces
运气好的话 他们不会久留
that with luck will not remain so for long.
或许我甚至发现了几个从前的对头
Perhaps I may even have spotted a few former foes of mine.
我要特别感谢你们的到来
I want especially to thank you for coming,
并感谢你们认识到自己的错误
and for seeing the error of your ways.
这些年来
Over these considerable years,
我非常满意意识到
I've learnt to my great satisfaction
没有比行善 无私奉献以及
there is no better way to cleanse the soul
为他人做出牺牲的善良行为
than to do good to perform selfless deeds
更好的净化灵魂的方法了
and acts of kindness to sacrifice for others,
最重要的是慷慨地给予
and most importantly to give generously.
正是由于你们的慷慨精神
It is due to your generous spirit
我们才能够丰富和改善
that we've been able to enrich and enhance
很多急需护理的婴儿 儿童 年轻男女
the lives of so many infants, children, young men and women
的生活
in desperate need of care
达到没有你们每个人的奉献就无法达到的水平
to a degree that would have been impossible to achieve without every one of you.
女士们 先生们 感谢你们今晚让我有幸成为款待你们的主人
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for the privilege of being your host tonight.
允许我为一个有价值的事业把手伸进
And for allowing me to slide my hands into your pockets and purses,
你们的口袋和钱包
but for a worthy a cause.
圣基特里娅的修女们做了杰出的工作... 所以
The sisters of St. Quiteria do outstanding work... So...
...真诚的付出
...Give with your heart.
检测到活动
海耶斯先生 作为一个已经死了三十年的人 你看起来真的很好
You look really good for a man who's been dead thirty years, Mr. Hayes.
你怎么进来的?
How'd you get in here?
技术 总有一天它会摧毁我们所有人
Technology. It just gonna fuck us all one day.
你是谁?
Who are you?
当地球上有人决定你的时间结束后
I'm the big bad wolf that comes to get you
我就是来抓你的大灰狼
when someone on this Earth decides your time is up.
穆迪
Moody.
复活很烦人 不是吗?
Resurrection is a bitch, ain't it?
你是来杀我的 是吗?
You've come to finish the job, haven't you?
对了 多年前你曾雇我来杀了你 对吧?
Well, you did hire me all those years ago to kill you, right?
那辆车里到底是谁?
Who was really in that car?
这重要吗? 那是可消耗资产 没人会在乎
Does it matter? Disposable asset. No one of any consequence.
这就是我希望像你这样的人满嘴的胡说八道
You see, that's the kind of shit I expect someone like you to say.
“没有人会在乎”
"No one of any consequence."
“像我这样的人”?
"Someone like me"?
老兄 我并不完全按道德原则行事
Man, I can't be all morally right.
我以杀人为生 坏人 请注意 但都是一样的
I kill people for a living, bad people, mind you, but still.
但我从不假装自己是别的什么
I never pretend to be anything else.
你 你是十几个著名慈善机构的代言人和核心人物
You, you're front and center of a dozen high-profile charitable causes.
全世界都认为你像他妈的初雪一样干净
The world sees you as clean as first fucking snow.
但你的手上全是屎
But your hands are covered in shit.
杀人 从沙林毒气到贩卖人口无所不有
Blood, everything from sarin gas to human trafficking.
所以你知道我为什么要安排我的死亡
So you know why I had to arrange my demise.
我有个儿子
I had a son,
在许多方面都与众不同
unexpected in many ways.
但我无法想象我对这个孩子
But what I couldn't fathom was the depths of love
对爱有多深
I had for this child,
这个不完美 非凡而脆弱的男孩
this imperfect, wonderful, vulnerable boy.
如果我死了 卢卡斯就不会受到任何威胁或伤害
If I were dead, Lucas would be free from any threats or harm.
胡说
Bullshit.
你可能爱你的儿子 海耶斯先生
You may love your son, Mr. Hayes,
但那只是你消失的借口
but that was your chance to disappear.
你很精明
You're very astute.
没人会去注意一个死了的人
No one looks for a dead man.
我就能继续躲在体面的裹尸布后面 让我...
I was able to continue behind the shroud of respectability that allowed me to...
成为一个更大的怪兽
To become a bigger monster.
讽刺的是 海耶斯先生
The irony of all of this, Mr. Hayes,
我只是想弥补你儿子我把你从他
is that I was just trying to make amends to your son
身边带走造成的伤害
for taking his father away from him.
这一切都是你自己造成的
You brought all of this on yourself.
安娜
Anna.
你看起来不太好
You don't look so good.
我不知道
I don't know.
没什么是一杯苹果马提尼
Nothing an Apple Martini and
和一升AB型血不能解决的 是吧?
a liter of AB positive won't fix, huh?
嘿 你觉得我得到这两样东西的机会有多大?
Hey, what do you think the chances are of me getting either?
不大
Faint.
有很有趣吗?
Something funny?
我觉得很有趣 你觉得你比我更好
I find it amusing you think you're better than me.
不是更好
Not better.
而是不同
Different.
你看 大多数人都很好 海耶斯先生
You see, most people are good, Mr. Hayes.
他们偶尔会做一些他们知道不好的事情
Then occasionally they do something they know is bad.
有些人是坏人 他们每天都在努力控制自己
Some people are bad, and they struggle every day to keep it under control.
其他人... 腐败到了极点 也不在乎 那就是我
Others... corrupt to the core and just don't give a damn, that would be me.
但是恶魔...
But evil...
恶魔是完全不同的生物 海耶斯先生
Evil is a completely different creature, Mr. Hayes.
恶魔相信坏是好的
Evil believes bad is okay,
它的行为是正当的
its actions are justified.
良心之外的暴力
Violence divorced from conscience,
它不管要付出什么代价 也不管对谁造成伤害
no matter what toll it takes or who it takes it upon.
就就是我们不同的地方 我的朋友
And there, my friend, is where we part ways.
我只是一个想寻找赎罪方法的坏人
I'm just a bad man who's looking to pay for his sins.
我知道
I see.
所以你来这里首先是为澄清你的良心?
So you are here to clear your conscience first?
你决不会活着离开这里
You'll never get out of here alive.
我从没打算活着离开
I never intended to.
还有一件事
One more thing.
你本可以杀了那个老头
You could have killed the old man.
你为什么不呢?
Why didn't you?
那不是计划
That wasn't the plan.
安娜: 这是个爆炸 位置
放开我
Leave me alone!
不 不
No! No!
不 妈妈
No! Mom!
妈妈
Mom!
你干什么去了?
What took you?
就是去吃个饭
Just out for a bite.
你就站在那里吗?
You just gonna stand there?
现在
For now.
不一定要这样 安娜
It doesn't have to be this way, Anna.
不再是了
Not anymore.
我们最终都要为自己的罪恶付出代价
We all have to pay for our sins eventually.
但不一定是今天
Doesn't have to be today.
我累了
I'm tired.
我想要平静
I want peace.
你在外面时我无法得到它
And I can't have it while you're out there.
如果我告诉你 你可以呢?
What if I told you you could?
什么?
Yeah?
在后脑勺开两枪 然后做个三明治
Two in the back of the head, and then go have a sandwich.
你无法改变你的过去 安娜
You can't buy back your past, Anna,
无法改变你的出身
can't change where you came from,
但是你可以改变你要去的方向
but you can change where you're going.
那会在哪里呢?
Where would that be?
导  演
马 丁·坎 贝 尔
编  剧
理 查 德·温 克
音  乐
鲁 伯 特·帕 克 斯
主  演
迈 克 尔·基 顿
李 美 琪
以  及
塞 缪 尔·杰 克 逊
门  徒